Arthur Glowka Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 8. Long Island Sound Study, 1961 - 2013; 8; Boxes: 19 - 22
  - Subseries 8.1: Committee Papers, 1961 - 2012; 8.1; Boxes: 19 - 20
    - Long Island Sound Study, 2004 - 2010 (Folder 1, Box 20)
    - Long Island Sound Study, 1961 - 2011 (Folder 2, Box 20)
    - Long Island Sound Study, 1993 - 2010 (Folder 3, Box 20)
    - Long Island Sound Study, 1997 - 2005 (Folder 4, Box 20)
  - Subseries 8.2: Financials, 1992 - 2013; 8.2; Boxes: 20 - 21
    - CAC money action, 2003 - 2013 (Folder 5, Box 20)
    - Federal Funding, 1992 - 2013 (Folder 6, Box 20)
    - Long Island Sound Committee Funding, 1991 - 2011 (Folder 1, Box 21)
    - Long Island Sound Committee Funding, 2008 - 2012 (Folder 2, Box 21)
  - Subseries 8.3: Programs, Plans, Reports, 1993 - 2010; 8.3; Boxes: 21 - 22
    - The Long Island Sound Foundation, 2004, 2010 (Folder 3, Box 21)
    - Long Island Sound Study: Comprehensive Conservation and Management Plan Tracking Report, 2000, 2009 (Folder 4, Box 21)
    - Long Island Sound Study: Comprehensive Conservation and Management Plan Tracking Report, 2001, 2010 (Folder 5, Box 21)
    - Long Island Sound Study: The Comprehensive Conservation and Management March Plan 1994 (Folder 6, Box 21)
    - Long Island Sound Study: The Comprehensive Conservation and Management March Plan 1994 (Folder 7, Box 21)
    - Long Island Sound Study: The Comprehensive Conservation and Management March Plan 1994 (Folder 1, Box 22)
    - Comprehensive Management Plan, 2001 - 2005 (Folder 2, Box 22)
    - Long Island Sound Study Report, 2008 (Folder 3, Box 22)
    - Long Island Sound Study Comprehensive Conservation and Management Plan Support Document, 1993 (Folder 4, Box 22)
- 9. Marine Life, 9
  Series contains materials on marine ecosystems, lobsters, and maritime animals
  - Subseries 9.1: Ecosystem, 9.1
  - Subseries 9.2: Lobsters, 9.2
  - Subseries 9.3: Maritime Animals, 9.3
- 10. Miscellaneous: Various Article Clippings, 1972 - 2013; 10; Boxes: 22 - 23
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, 1996 - 2010 (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, 2006 (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, 2008 (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, undated (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, 1992 - 2013 (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - Items, undated (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - Scientists, 2008 (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996 - 2011 (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2012 (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000 - 2011 (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - Data - Miscellaneous, 1972 - 2006 (Folder 8, Box 23)
- 11. New York, 1913 - 2012; 11; Boxes: 24 - 26
  Series contains materials on NY environment and legal action about the environment.
  - Subseries 11.1: Environment, 1913 - 2012; 11.1; Boxes: 24 - 26
    - Water Quality, 1983 - 2005 (Folder 1, Box 24)
    - Water Quality, 1995 - 2011 (Folder 2, Box 24)
    - Water Quality, 1993 - 1999 (Folder 3, Box 24)
    - Water Quality, 1993 - 2008 (Folder 4, Box 24)
    - Water Quality, 1985 - 2009 (Folder 5, Box 24)
    - Animals, 2003 - 2009 (Folder 6, Box 24)
    - Marine Counsel Commission, 2006 - 2011 (Folder 7, Box 24)
    - Fish, 1998 - 2002 (Folder 1, Box 25)
    - Environment, 1995 - 2011 (Folder 2, Box 25)
    - Environment, 1993 - 2009 (Folder 3, Box 25)
    - Environment, 1983 - 2012 (Folder 4, Box 25)
    - Environment, 1998 - 2008 (Folder 5, Box 25)
    - Environment, 1998 - 2008 (Folder 6, Box 25)
    - Environment, 1913 - 2009 (Folder 7, Box 25)
    - Poughkeepsie, undated (Folder 1, Box 26)
    - Breakwater, 2010 (Folder 2, Box 26)
    - Tides, 2006 - 2008 (Folder 3, Box 26)
    - East River and Long Island Sound, 2000 - 2008 (Folder 4, Box 26)
    - Estuary, 1997 (Folder 5, Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 2004 - 2006 (Folder 6, Box 26)
  - Subseries 11.2: Environment and Legal Action, 1972 - 2011; 11.2; Box: 26
    - New York Legal Action / Advocacy, 1992 - 2009 (Folder 7, Box 26)
    - New York Legal Action / Advocacy, 2005 - 2011 (Folder 8, Box 26)
    - New York Correspondence, 2003 - 2011 (Folder 9, Box 26)
    - New York and the Hudson, 1972 - 2003 (Folder 10, Box 26)
- 12. Publications, 1909 - 2013; 12; Boxes: 26 - 39
  Series contains article clippings or publications on the Chesapeake Bay, Connecticut, Maine, Ecosystems, Environment and Science, Fishing, The Long Island Sound, New York, Rhose Island, Marine Life, Fish, Marine Life and Science, Miscellaneous Science, and Science.
  - Subseries 12.1: Chesapeake Bay, Connecticut, Maine Article Clippings, 1988 - 2012; 12.1; Boxes: 26 - 27
    - Chesapeake Bay and Animals, 1998 - 2011 (Folder 11, Box 26)
    - Chesapeake Bay and Animals, 2002 - 2012 (Folder 12, Box 26)
    - Connecticut and advocacy, 1999 - 2012 (Folder 13, Box 26)
    - Chesapeake Bay and Marine Life, 2003 - 2009 (Folder 14, Box 26)
    - Connecticut and animals, 1988 - 2012 (Folder 1, Box 27)
    - Maine, 2011 (Folder 2, Box 27)
  - Subseries 12.2: Ecosystem Article Clippings, 1973 - 2012; 12.2; Boxes: 27 - 29
    - Tides, 1982 - 2010 (Folder 3, Box 27)
    - Start of plants, 1996 - 2012 (Folder 4, Box 27)
    - Ecosystem, 1995 - 2013 (Folder 5, Box 27)
    - Ecosystem, 1992 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 27)
    - Water Quality, 1995 - 2010 (Folder 1, Box 28)
    - Water Quality, 1996 - 2010 (Folder 2, Box 28)
    - Estuary, 2000 - 2009 (Folder 3, Box 28)
    - Land Environment, 1973 - 2012 (Folder 4, Box 28)
    - Marine Environment, 1986 - 2012 (Folder 5, Box 28)
    - Aquatic Ecosystems, 1994 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 28)
    - Aquatic Ecosystems, 1996 - 2013 (Folder 1, Box 29)
    - Aquatic Ecosystems, 2003 - 2012 (Folder 2, Box 29)
    - Aquatic Ecosystems, 1999 - 2012 (Folder 3, Box 29)
  - Subseries 12.3: Environment and Science Article Clippings, 1990 - 2013; 12.3; Boxes: 30 - 31
    - Environment, 1999 - 2012 (Folder 1, Box 30)
    - Oceans, Bays, Streams, 1995 - 2012 (Folder 2, Box 30)
    - Oceans, Bays, Streams, 1990 - 2010 (Folder 3, Box 30)
    - Oceans, Bays, Streams, 1990 - 2012 (Folder 4, Box 30)
    - Animals, 1996 - 2012 (Folder 1, Box 31)
    - Science, 1995 - 2013 (Folder 2, Box 31)
    - Science, 1997 - 2013 (Folder 3, Box 31)
    - Science, 1994 - 2013 (Folder 4, Box 31)
    - Health Articles, 1995 - 2013 (Folder 5, Box 31)
    - Start of Microbes, 2006 - 2013 (Folder 6, Box 31)
    - Nitrogen, 2001 - 2013 (Folder 7, Box 31)
  - Subseries 12.4: Fishing Article Clippings, 1997 - 2013; 12.4; Boxes: 31 - 32
    - Connecticut Coastal Angler, 1998 - 2000 (Folder 1, Box 31)
    - Fishing Correspondence, 1996 - 2011 (Folder 2, Box 31)
    - Science and Fishing Reports, undated (Folder 3, Box 31)
    - Aquaculture II, 1991 - 2012 (Folder 4, Box 31)
    - Fishery Articles, 1999 - 2011 (Folder 5, Box 31)
    - Fishery Academic Articles, 1981 - 2011 (Folder 6, Box 31)
    - Fishery Council, 2005 - 2012 (Folder 7, Box 31)
    - Halloween Yacht Club, 2007 - 2012 (Folder 8, Box 31)
    - Fishing Articles, 2001 - 2012 (Folder 9, Box 31)
    - The Fisherman, 1998 - 2013 (Folder 1, Box 32)
    - The Fisherman, 1997 - 2013 (Folder 2, Box 32)
  - Subseries 12.5: Long Island Sound, New York, Rhode Island Article Clippings, 1909 - 2013; 12.5; Box: 32
    - New York, 1909 - 2009 (Folder 3, Box 32)
    - The Sound and Animals, 1960 - 2012 (Folder 4, Box 32)
    - The Sound and Advocacy, 1991 - 2011 (Folder 5, Box 32)
  - Subseries 12.6: Marine Life, 1963 - 2000; 12.6; Boxes: 33 - 24
    - Saltwater Sportsman, 1969 (Folder 1, Box 33)
    - Saltwater Sportsman, 1980 - 1982 (Folder 2, Box 33)
    - Saltwater Sportsman, 1994 (Folder 3, Box 33)
    - Saltwater Sportsman, 2003 - 2005 (Folder 4, Box 33)
    - Fishing Annual, 1966 - 1975 (Folder 5, Box 33)
    - Pennsylvania Angler, 1963 - 1976 (Folder 6, Box 33)
    - Saltwater Sportsman, 1978 - 1979 (Folder 7, Box 33)
    - Saltwater Sportsman, 1970 - 1973 (Folder 2, Box 34)
    - Connecticut - Rhode Island - The Fisherman, 1975 (Folder 3, Box 34)
    - New England Edition - The Fisherman, 1984 - 2000 (Folder 4, Box 34)
    - Long Island Fisherman, 1979 (Folder 5, Box 34)
    - New Jersey Edition - Fisherman, 1973 - 1976 (Folder 6, Box 34)
    - Field and Stream, 1969 - 1972 (Folder 7, Box 34)
    - Field and Stream, 1965 - 1979 (Folder 8, Box 34)
  - Subseries 12.7: Marine Life Article Clippings, 1975 - 2013; 12.7; Boxes: 35 - 37
    - Mollusks, 1989 - 2009 (Folder 2, Box 35)
    - Worms, 1989 - 2009 (Folder 3, Box 35)
    - Jellyfish, 2002 - 2013 (Folder 4, Box 35)
    - "Red" Tide Issues, 1981 - 2009 (Folder 5, Box 35)
    - Horseshoe Crabs, 2006 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 35)
    - Sea Squirt, 2005 - 2006 (Folder 7, Box 35)
    - Eels, 1996 - 2012 (Folder 8, Box 35)
    - Crabs, 2003 - 2011 (Folder 9, Box 35)
    - Limpets, 2005 (Folder 10, Box 35)
    - Fish, 1996 - 2013 (Folder 11, Box 35)
    - Fish, 1997 - 2011 (Folder 12, Box 35)
    - Fish, 1985 - 2013 (Folder 13, Box 35)
    - Fish, 1988 - 2011 (Folder 1, Box 36)
    - Fish, 1980 - 1985 (Folder 2, Box 36)
    - Fish, 1999 - 2011 (Folder 3, Box 36)
    - Marine Life, 1997 - 2011 (Folder 4, Box 36)
    - Shrimp, 2004 - 2012 (Folder 5, Box 36)
    - Invasive Species, 1999 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 36)
    - Seafood, 1978 - 2012 (Folder 7, Box 36)
    - Plant Life, 1985 - 2012 (Folder 8, Box 36)
    - Menhaden, 1975 - 2010 (Folder 1, Box 37)
    - Menhaden, 1987 - 2011 (Folder 2, Box 37)
    - Menhaden, 1985 - 2011 (Folder 3, Box 37)
    - Bass, 1991 - 2013 (Folder 4, Box 37)
  - Subseries 12.8: Fish Related Article Clippings, 1973 - 2013; 12.8; Box: 37
    - Shad, Tautog, Trout, 2007 - 2012 (Folder 5, Box 37)
    - Cod, 2002 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 37)
    - Groundfish, 2007 - 2008 (Folder 7, Box 37)
    - Herring, 2002 - 2013 (Folder 8, Box 37)
    - Tuna, 2011 (Folder 9, Box 37)
    - Flounder / Flatfish, 1973 - 2008 (Folder 10, Box 37)
    - Bait Articles, 2007 - 2013 (Folder 11, Box 37)
    - Political Action and Fishing, 1993 - 2013 (Folder 12, Box 37)
    - Political Action and Fishing, 2000 - 2013 (Folder 1, Box 37)
    - Political Action and Fishing, 1978 - 2013 (Folder 2, Box 37)
    - Political Action and Fishing, 2001 - 2012 (Folder 3, Box 37)
  - Subseries 12.9: Marine Life and Science Article, 1993 - 2012; 12.9; Box: 37
    - Weather, 1993 - 1998 (Folder 4, Box 37)
    - Birds, 1998 - 2011 (Folder 5, Box 37)
    - Birds, 1999 - 2012 (Folder 6, Box 37)
    - Sewage, pollution, manure, 1997 - 2012 (Folder 7, Box 37)
  - Subseries 12.10: Science Miscellaneous, 12.10; Box: 38
  - Subseries 12.11: Science, 1961 - 2006; 12.11; Boxes: 38 - 39
    - Outdoor Life, 1964 - 1980 (Folder 1, Box 38)
    - Outdoor Life, 1971 - 1976 (Folder 2, Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous Outdoor Magazines, 1961 - 1977 (Folder 3, Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous Outdoor Magazines, 1966 - 1972 (Folder 4, Box 38)
    - Science Magazines, 1971 - 1975 (Folder 1, Box 39)
    - Elderidge Tide and Pilot Book, 2002 - 2006 (Folder 2, Box 39)
- 13. Videos, 13; Boxes: 39 - 40
  - Amazon Part 1 original, undated (Folder 3, Box 39)
  - Amazon Part 1 copy, undated (Folder 1, Box 40)
  - Kokanee King, undated (Folder 2, Box 40)
  - Kokanee King copy, undated (Folder 3, Box 40)
  - Belem Para, undated (Folder 4, Box 40)
- 14. Oversized Graphic Materials, 14; Box: 41
  - Subseries 14.1: Oversized Graphic Materials, 14.1; Folders: 1 - 6; Box: 41
    - New York Graphic Material, undated (Folder 1, Box 41)
    - Aviation Pictures, undated (Folder 2, Box 41)
    - Aquatic Maps and Posters, 2001 - 2013 (Folder 3, Box 41)
    - Connecticut and Long Island, 1920 - 1998 (Folder 4, Box 41)
    - Envitonmental, 2004 - 2012 (Folder 5, Box 41)
    - Political, 2001 (Folder 6, Box 41)
  - Subseries 14.2: Maps of Connecticut, 14.2
  - Subseries 14.3: Maps of Long Island, 14.3
  - Subseries 14.4: Maps Miscellaneous, 14.4
  - Subseries 14.5: Maps of New York, 14.5
  - Subseries 14.6: Poster, 14.6
- 15. Awards, 1909 - 2013; 15; Box: 42
  - Hudson River Fishermen' s Association Award, 1974 (Folder 1, Box 42)
  - Hudson River Fishermans Association Award, 1975 (Folder 2, Box 42)